When someone you love dies... are they gone forever?
Dragonfly is a drama, thriller, fantasy film directed by Tom Shadyac.
A grieving doctor is being contacted by his late wife
through his patient's near death experiences.
Joe Darrow, played by Kevin Costner.
Hugh Campbell, played by Joe Morton.
Charlie Dickinson, played by Ron Rifkin.
Emily Darrow, played by Susanna Thompson.
Mrs. Belmont, played by Kathy Bates.
Ben, played by Jacob Smith.
Dragonfly is a 2002 supernatural drama thriller film directed by Tom Shadyac from a screenplay by
Brandon Camp, Mike Thompson, and David Seltzer based on a story by Camp and Thompson.
The film was produced by Gary Barber, Roger Birnbaum, Mark Johnson, and Shadyac.
It stars Kevin Costner as a grieving doctor being contacted by his
dead wife through his patients' near-death experiences.
Upon release, Dragonfly was a critical and commercial failure, with the film only grossing $52.3 million against its $60 million production
budget and was universally panned by critics, who described it as "sappy, dull and muddled" and "too melancholic and cliched".
The film explores themes of pregnancy, car crash, dragonfly, jungle, hospital.
The tone is emotional and intense.